AFIF HAFIZIN BIN HAMIZAN

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 0142321612, afifhafizin13@gmail.com

PROFILE	A passionate fresh graduate computer science student with 2 years of invaluable experience in developing website Equipped with the ability to escalate brand awareness by utilizing skills gained in the information technology industry, being able to identify opportunities and overcome objections to establishing a successful and lucrative company.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
May 2023 — Current	Full Stack Web Deve	loper, Universiti Ma	alaya (UM)	Kuala Lumpur
	 Utilized PHP, JQuery and HTML in developing some functional pages for the UM FIRST on payment module. Utilized Postgres for storing data for the UM FIRSTPRO. Provide maintenance services for UM FIRSTPRO website. 			
Sep 2022 — Mar 2023	Full Stack Web Developer, UM Innovations Sdn Bhd			Kuala Lumpur
	 Utilized PHP, JQuery and HTML in developing some functional pages for the UM FIRSTPRO focused on payment module. Utilized Postgres for storing data for the UM FIRSTPRO. 			
Oct 2021 — Feb 2022	UIUX Designer, Tombark Technology Sdn Bhd Selangor			
		n designing Graphical User Ilustrator and other comput	, ,	and dekstop version. alize logo design and creative
EDUCATION				
Sep 2018 — Aug 2022	Bachelor of Computer Science (Graphics and Multimedia Software), Universiti Teknologi Malaysia			
	Graduated with Honors in Graphics and Multimedia Software			
Jun 2017 — May 2018	Matriculation, Selangor Matriculation College			Selangor
	Sijil Matrikulasi			
Jan 2012 — Dec 2016	Secondary School, SMK Seri Tasik Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)			Kuala Lumpur
SKILLS	HTML	Experienced	Jquery	Experienced
	PHP	Experienced	Postgres	Experienced

JavaScript

Flutter

Laravel

Ajax

Dart

MVC

Experienced

Experienced

Experienced

Experienced

Experienced

Experienced